<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Programming on My Writings - Priyanshu Verma</title><link>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/tags/programming/</link><description>Recent content in Programming on My Writings - Priyanshu Verma</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 11:49:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/tags/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploy Fluvio with Cloud Cluster for free.</title><link>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/deploy-fluvio-with-cloud-cluster-for-free./</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 11:49:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/deploy-fluvio-with-cloud-cluster-for-free./</guid><description>Hello builders, Many of you knows me but in case I am Priyanshu Verma, An Open-source Indie Developer.
In this Article we are going to talk about how you can deploy Fluvio integrated apps like APIs on internet for free. It is very easy to do so, As Today I will guide you how to. So, Without any delay let&rsquo;s see what to do.
As To deploy fluvio we need a project with it&rsquo;s integration. I have one from recent Fluvio Series. This is a basic Nodejs Express API with some endpoints and fluvio integration. I won&rsquo;t explain more about it you can explore this on GitHub. This article is just for deployment.</description></item><item><title>Fluvio - An open-source In-motion data framework.</title><link>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/fluvio---an-open-source-in-motion-data-framework./</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:59:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/fluvio---an-open-source-in-motion-data-framework./</guid><description>Hello enthusiasts,
Today we are going to learn about Fluvio work with this technology. This post is not about theory it&rsquo;s a practical based article. You can checkout Fluvio&rsquo;s own blogs to learn about fluvio deep.
Why to read this article? Yes, you can find the documentation about Fluvio in the corners of internet but you can&rsquo;t get a end-to-end project that&rsquo;s what this article provides you. Believe me at the end you will find yourself confident with fluvio and one simple yet complex project. Let&rsquo;s dive right in!</description></item><item><title>Showcase Your Achievements Securely with CertiFolio 🚀</title><link>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/showcase-your-achievements-securely-with-certifolio-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 03:48:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/showcase-your-achievements-securely-with-certifolio-/</guid><description>Hello Dev.to community!
We&rsquo;re thrilled to introduce CertiFolio, a groundbreaking platform designed to securely upload, showcase, and verify your certificates and achievements using the power of the InterPlanetary File System (IPFS).
Why CertiFolio? In today’s digital age, managing and verifying your credentials can be cumbersome and insecure. CertiFolio leverages decentralized storage to offer a robust, user-friendly solution to this problem. Here’s a sneak peek into what makes CertiFolio unique:
🌟 Features Decentralized Storage: Store your certificates on IPFS for secure, permanent access, eliminating the risk of centralized data breaches. Verification: Utilize blockchain technology to ensure the authenticity of your certificates, making verification seamless and trustworthy. User-Friendly Interface: Our intuitive design simplifies the process of uploading, viewing, and managing your achievements. 🚀 Getting Started Ready to take CertiFolio for a spin? Follow these steps to set up and start using the platform:</description></item><item><title>Custom SSO Implementation</title><link>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/custom-sso-implementation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 03:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/custom-sso-implementation/</guid><description>The SSO Implementation repository contains the implementation details and examples for seamlessly integrating the SSO Service into your applications.
Repository Link SSO Implementation Repository
Features 1. Example Integrations Explore comprehensive examples demonstrating how to integrate the SSO Service into various types of applications, providing a foundation for seamless authentication and authorization.
2. Usage Guidelines Clear and detailed guidelines on using the SSO Service within your applications, ensuring a smooth and secure single sign-on experience for end-users.</description></item><item><title>Saavn Music Player for Windows</title><link>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/saavn-music-player-for-windows/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:25:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/saavn-music-player-for-windows/</guid><description>Welcome to the Saavn Music Player for Windows, an open-source desktop application that allows you to enjoy your favorite music seamlessly. This music player is powered by the Saavn API and built with Flutter, providing a robust and modern user experience.
Features Seamless Music Playback: Enjoy high-quality music playback with an intuitive interface. Search and Discover: Use the Saavn API to search for your favorite songs, albums, and artists. Playlist Management: Create and manage your playlists easily. Rich Metadata: View detailed metadata for each track, including album art, artist information, and more. Cross-Platform: Built with Flutter, ensuring a consistent experience across different devices. Installation To install the Saavn Music Player for Windows, follow these steps:</description></item><item><title>Checkcup - Browserless Puppetter Project Build.</title><link>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/checkcup---browserless-puppetter-project-build./</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 09:48:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/checkcup---browserless-puppetter-project-build./</guid><description>Checkcup Checkcup is a website monitoring tool that fetches the status of websites along with screenshots and active status. It is built using Next.js for the frontend and Puppeteer with Browserless in the backend.
Features Fetches website status including HTTP status code, response time, and active status. Captures screenshots of websites for visual verification. Supports monitoring multiple websites simultaneously. Demo {% embed https://github.com/priyanshuverma-dev/quine-checkcup %}
Live Preview You can view a live preview of Checkcup here.</description></item></channel></rss>