<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fluvio on My Writings - Priyanshu Verma</title><link>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/tags/fluvio/</link><description>Recent content in Fluvio on My Writings - Priyanshu Verma</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 11:49:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/tags/fluvio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploy Fluvio with Cloud Cluster for free.</title><link>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/deploy-fluvio-with-cloud-cluster-for-free./</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 11:49:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/deploy-fluvio-with-cloud-cluster-for-free./</guid><description>Hello builders, Many of you knows me but in case I am Priyanshu Verma, An Open-source Indie Developer.
In this Article we are going to talk about how you can deploy Fluvio integrated apps like APIs on internet for free. It is very easy to do so, As Today I will guide you how to. So, Without any delay let&rsquo;s see what to do.
As To deploy fluvio we need a project with it&rsquo;s integration. I have one from recent Fluvio Series. This is a basic Nodejs Express API with some endpoints and fluvio integration. I won&rsquo;t explain more about it you can explore this on GitHub. This article is just for deployment.</description></item><item><title>Yes, It's easy to build a Fluvio connector in Rust.</title><link>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/yes-its-easy-to-build-a-fluvio-connector-in-rust./</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 07:32:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/yes-its-easy-to-build-a-fluvio-connector-in-rust./</guid><description>In today’s fast-paced world, real-time data is no longer a luxury—it’s a necessity. Whether you&rsquo;re monitoring live stock prices, analyzing social media trends, or syncing spreadsheets for instant insights, having data at your fingertips can make all the difference. That’s where Fluvio comes in, a platform designed to streamline your data journey by offering a powerful, yet easy-to-use, infrastructure for building and managing data pipelines.
But here’s the real magic of Fluvio: It gives you the tools to not only move data between systems but also build your very own custom connectors! Imagine you’re working with Google Sheets, and you want your data to flow seamlessly from a Fluvio topic into a spreadsheet in real-time. Manually exporting data sounds tedious, right? What if you could build an outbound connector that does all this for you automatically?</description></item><item><title>Fluvio - An open-source In-motion data framework.</title><link>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/fluvio---an-open-source-in-motion-data-framework./</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:59:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://priyanshuverma-dev.github.io/blogs/fluvio---an-open-source-in-motion-data-framework./</guid><description>Hello enthusiasts,
Today we are going to learn about Fluvio work with this technology. This post is not about theory it&rsquo;s a practical based article. You can checkout Fluvio&rsquo;s own blogs to learn about fluvio deep.
Why to read this article? Yes, you can find the documentation about Fluvio in the corners of internet but you can&rsquo;t get a end-to-end project that&rsquo;s what this article provides you. Believe me at the end you will find yourself confident with fluvio and one simple yet complex project. Let&rsquo;s dive right in!</description></item></channel></rss>